Guide to the Seymour Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Charles Seymour, Jr., (1918-1975)-[1978]; Series XIV; 5' (12 boxes)
  - Courses
    - American University course, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 221)
    - History of Art I, Yale University, 1955-1956 (Box 85, Folder 222)
    - Course on Nanni di Banco, 1957 (Box 85, Folder 223)
    - History of Art I, Yale University, 1957-1959 (Box 85, Folder 224)
    - Summer school, University of Colorado, 1958, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 225)
    - "Michelangelo: The Artist and His World," Yale Art Gallery Associates lecture course, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 226)
    - Hartford College lecture course on sculpture, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 227)
    - Yale T.V. series: survey of Italian painting, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 228)
    - "The Renaissance City," Yale Art Gallery Associates lecture course, undated (Box 86, Folder 229)
    - "Western Art," Congresswomen's Club course, undated (Box 86, Folder 230)
    - Illustrative architectural drawings, undated (Box 86, Folder 231)
  - Printed Material
    - Yale College, 1934-1935 (Box 86, Folder 232)
    - Book announcements, programs, publicity for lectures, 1951-1973, undated (Box 86, Folder 233)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1939-1970, undated (Box 86, Folder 234)
    - Miscellaneous, 1922-1968 (Box 86, Folder 235)
  - Personal and Memorabilia
    - Infant's knitted mittens, undated (Box 86, Folder 236)
    - Yale College memorabilia, 1930-1933 (Box 86, Folder 237)
    - Le Lorrain material, undated (Box 86, Folder 238-239)
    - World War II memorabilia, 1939-1945 (Box 86, Folder 240)
    - Photograph of "River Deities," from Boston Museum of Fine Arts, undated (Box 86, Folder 241)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 86, Folder 242)
    - Academic biography, undated (Box 86, Folder 243)
    - Passports: Charles Seymour, Jr., 1924-1962 (Box 86, Folder 244)
    - Passports: Charlotte (Ball) Seymour, 1954, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 245)
- Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, 1918-1969; Series XV; 5" (2 boxes)
  Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, Charles and Gladys Seymour's middle child, attended Rosemary Hall and Le Cours Maintenon in Cannes, France, and spent a year in Paris studying French literature and art.
  She settled in Washington, D.C., where she worked at Studio House, which was connected with the Phillips Memorial Gallery. She later became assistant director of the Federal Arts Project, the arts section of the Works Progress Administration.
  During World War II, Elizabeth, known as Betsey, worked with the Office of Strategic Services in Washington, North Africa (where she was part of the original O.S.S. contingent which arrived just after the Allied landing), and Europe.
  After the war, Betsey returned to New Haven, where she lived with her parents. She worked for a time on the secretarial and administrative staff of the Veterans Administration Hospital in West Haven, then became secretary to Judge Thomas W. Swan of the Second U.S. District Court. She died the day before her birthday, on February 9, 1969.
  This series is divided into three sections.
  Correspondence contains letters to Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, arranged alphabetically by sender and chronologically within each folder. These are followed by letters from Elizabeth Atwater Seymour to non-family members, which are arranged alphabetically by recipient.
  Personal and Memorabilia consists of Elizabeth Atwater Seymour's mementoes of the schools she attended and of her experiences in the Office of Strategic Services, her last will and testament and probate information, and a folder of miscellaneous material.
  Formely Restricted Material consists of one half-size box of family correspondence which was closed until January 1, 2000, by request of the donor.
  - Correspondence
    - Elizabeth Atwater Seymour from
      - [Hemingway?], Louise, 1934 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Howard, James M., III, 1956, undated (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - [St. John, George, Jr.?], undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1918-1922, 1944-1945, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Seymour, Charles, Jr., 1950 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Seymour, Charles, III, undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Seymour, Charlotte (Ball), 1946, 1953 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Seymour, Charlotte, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Sichel, L.J., 1943 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified, 1936-1961, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Elizabeth Atwater Seymour to
      - Hemingway, Louise, 1932-1956 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Seymour, L.C., 1933 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - "Steve", 1936 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Unidentified, 1930, undated (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Fragment, undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Personal and Memorabilia
    - School papers, 1923, undated (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - O.S.S. material, 1944 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Obituary notices, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1914-1941, undated (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Last will and testament, estate material
      See: box 108, folder 77
- Elizabeth Atwater Seymour (FORMERLY RESTRICTED MATERIAL), Series XV
  This is a listing of the contents of a 1/2-size box of family correspondence which was closed until January 1, 2000, by request of the donor.
  - Formerly Restricted Material
    - Elizabeth Atwater Seymour: to Seymour, Charles and Gladys, 1945, 1951-1952 (Box 103)
    - Elizabeth Atwater Seymour: to Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), 1941, 1951 (Box 103)
    - Charles Seymour (1885-1963): from Fasanello, Rocko, 1945 (Box 103)
    - Charles Seymour (1885-1963): from Kent, Sherman, 1945 (Box 103)
    - Gladys (Watkins) Seymour: from [King?], Bobbie, 1941 (Box 103)
- Howard Family, 1936-1956, undated; Series XVI; 0.25; (1 box)
  Sarah (Seymour) Howard, the youngest of Charles and Gladys Seymour's three children, was born July 4, 1920. Like her sister Betsey, Sarah, known as Sally, attended Le Cours Maintenon, Cannes, France. She graduated from the Westover School in 1938 and Vassar College in 1942.
  On September 25, 1942, Sally married James Merriam Howard, Jr., a senior at Yale. Three months later Jim Howard enlisted as a private in the U.S. Marine Corps. In March of 1943 he was commissioned a second lieutenant. During the period of his training Sally, like so many other war brides, traveled to be near the places he was stationed. He was eventually sent overseas to the South Pacific but returned to the United States in time for the birth of their son James M. Howard, III (Jerry) on March 19, 1944.
  The young Howard family moved to New Jersey where Jim had obtained a position teaching English at the Lawrenceville School. Early in December, 1945, Sally contracted infantile paralysis and died.
  Jerry Howard lived with his maternal grandparents until his father's marriage in 1949 to Selena Tatlock. Jim Howard remained at Lawrenceville until 1954, when he accepted the post of headmaster of Blair Academy, in Blairstown, New Jersey.
  This short series is divided into three sections.
  Correspondence contains letters to Sarah (Seymour) Howard, which are arranged alphabetically by sender and chronologically within each folder. There are also letters to others from her son, James Merriam Howard, III. These are arranged alphabetically by recipient and chronologically within each folder.
  Writings consists of one story composed by Sarah (Seymour) Howard when she was a child.
  Personal and Memorabilia contains only Sarah (Seymour) Howard's passport, dated 1932.
  - Correspondence
    - James M. Howard, Jr.: from Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1947 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Sarah (Seymour) Howard: from St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1936 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Sarah (Seymour) Howard: from Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1941 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Sarah (Seymour) Howard: from [Seymour, Charles, Jr.?], undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Sarah (Seymour) Howard: from Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater, 1944 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - James M. Howard, III: to [Stanton?], Louise, undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - James M. Howard, III: to "Uncle Howard", 1956 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Writings
    - Story by Sarah (Seymour) Howard, [ca 1930] (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Personal and Memorabilia
    - Sarah (Seymour) Howard: passport, 1932 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Leggett - Seymour - Doolittle Families, (1860-1896)-1954; Series XVII; 10" (2 boxes)
  Correspondence contains letters addressed to the following people:
  Laura Leggett (Seymour) Doolittle
  Thomas Benjamin Doolittle
  Leverett Leggett
  Marilla (Wells) Leggett
  Mortimer Dormer Leggett
  Mortimer Marcellus Leggett
  Wells Willner Leggett
  Henry Albert Seymour
  Mary Marilla (Leggett) Seymour
  For each recipient, the material is arranged alphabetically by sender. Within each folder the letters are arranged chronologically. At the end of the section there is correspondence from Mortimer Dormer Leggett and Wells Willner Leggett to non-family members.
  Writings consists of six notebooks concerning fravel and daily life, compiled by Laura Leggett (Seymour) Doolittle and a pamphlet for inventors by Henry Albert Seymour.
  Printed Material consists of newspaper clippings and obituaries, arranged alphabetically by the names of the deceased.
  Personal and Memorabilia contains a list of family correspondence conducted during the Civil War, an appraisal of the contents of Thistle Farm (the summer home of Laura (Seymour) Doolittle), and various mementoes saved by members of the family. The folders are arranged alphabetically by family member.
  - Correspondence
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: from Nicolay, Helen, 1952-1954 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: from Spellman, Francis Cardinal, 1952 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Thomas Benjamin Doolittle: from Cleveland, Grover, 1901 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Benjamin Doolittle: from Page, Thomas Nelson, 1904 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Leverett Leggett: from Leggett, Mortimer Dormer, 1862, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Leverett Leggett: from Leggett, Wells Willner, 1864-1865 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from A-Z, 1862-1864 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from Leggett, Leverett, 1863-1864 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from [Leggett, Mary (Strong)?], 1863, 1876 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from Leggett, Mortimer Dormer, 1860-1862 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      See also: box 108, folder 78
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from Leggett, Mortimer Dormer, 1863-1868 (Box 89, Folder 11-13)
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from Leggett, Wells Willner, 1862-1865 (Box 89, Folder 14-15)
      See also: box 108, folder 79
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from Seymour, Mary (Leggett), undated (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from [Wells?], Harriet, undated (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Mortimer Dormer Leggett: from A-Z, 1861, undated (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Mortimer Dormer Leggett: from Leggett, Marilla (Wells), 1864 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Mortimer Dormer Leggett: from [Leggett, Mary (Strong)?], 1861 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Mortimer Marcellus-Leggett: from Leggett, Mortimer Dormer, 1862-1865, 1873 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Mortimer Marcellus Leggett: from Leggett, Wells Willner, 1863-1864 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Wells Willner Leggett: from Strong, L.L., 1864 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Henry Albert Seymour: from A-Z, 1870, 1916 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Henry Albert Seymour: from Seymour, Mary (Leggett), 1873 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Marilla (Wells) Leggett (Mrs. Mortimer D. ): from Wells, Marilla (mother), 1862, undated (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Mary (Leggett) Seymour: from [Leggett, Mary (Strong)?], 1876 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Mary (Leggett) Seymour: from Leggett, Mortimer Dormer, 1862-1864 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Mary (Leggett) Seymour: from [Leggett, Mortimer Marcellus?], 1873 (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Mary (Leggett) Seymour: from Leggett, Wells Willner, 1864-1865 (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Mary (Leggett) Seymour: from Seymour, Henry Albert, 1896 (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - "Mother Wells": from Leggett, Mortimer Dormer, 1862 (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - Leverett Leggett: to unidentified, [1862] September 21 (Box 90, Folder 33a)
    - Mortimer Dormer Leggett: to Mr. Hardman, 1862 (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - Wells Willner Leggett: to A-Z, 1862, 1864 (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Writings
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: notebook, "Trip to England, 1929" (Box 90, Folder 36-38)
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: daily notes, miscellany, 1934-1949 (Box 90, Folder 39)
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: notebook, coronation of Queen Elizabeth II, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 40)
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: notebook, undated (Box 90, Folder 41)
    - Henry Albert Seymour: Information Valuable to Inventors, 1876 (Box 90, Folder 42)
  - Printed Material
    - News clippings: coronation of Queen Elizabeth II, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 43)
    - Obituary: Laura (Seymour) Doolittle, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 44)
    - Obituary: Marilla (Wells) Leggett, 1875 (Box 90, Folder 45)
    - Obituary: Mortimer Dormer Leggett, 1896 (Box 90, Folder 46)
    - Obituary: Helen Nicolay, 1954 (Box 90, Folder 47)
  - Personal and Memorabilia
    - List of Leggett family correspondence during the Civil War (Box 90, Folder 48)
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: memorabilia (Box 90, Folder 49)
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: appraisal of contents of Thimble Farm
      See: box 108, folder 80
    - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle: estate
      See: box 67, folder 137-138
    - Mortimer Leggett Doolittle: memorabilia, 1888, undated (Box 90, Folder 50)
    - Henry Albert Seymour certificate, 1881 (Box 90, Folder 51)
    - Mary (Leggett) Seymour: memorabilia, 1868, undated (Box 90, Folder 52)
- Photographs, 1859-1967; Series XVIII; 4'9.5" (12 boxes)
  People is arranged alphabetically by subject. For each person, the photographs are further divided into pictures of the individual alone, followed by group shots in which he is the principal or eldest person, followed by photographs taken by that person. Within each folder, the photographs are arranged chronologically.
  Places is arranged alphabetically by the name of the person or institution to whom the place belonged.
  Miscellaneous contains the seal of Seal of Thomas Seymour (1632-1712).
  - People
    - Andrews, Clara (Gilbert), 1860, undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Andrews, Catharine Augusta (Day), undated (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Andrews, Robert Day, 1874 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1876, 1890, 1900, 1927 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      See also: box 111, folder 98-99
      See also: box 114, folder 5
      See also: box 91, folder 8
      See also: box 100, folder 151
    - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour); Clara (Seymour) St. John, 1892-1899 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Angel, Elizabeth Day (seymour); Clara (Seymour) St. John; Harriet Day Parsons, 1888-1889 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Angel, John, 1918, undated (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Angel, John, at work on the Exeter War Memorial with description by Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, 1920 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Angel, John, work of, 1915-1923, undated (Box 91, Folder 9-10)
    - Angel, John; John Lawrence Angel; Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour, 1916 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Angel, John Lawrence, 1916 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Angel Family, 1915-1927, 1937, undated (Box 91, Folder 13-14)
    - Barnes, Mollie; Charles Seymour, Jr., [1913-1914?] (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Chenevard, Mary Juliana (Seymour), undated (Box 91, Folder 16-17)
    - [Christie Family?], 1920-1922, undated (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Day, Ellen, 1894 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Day, Mary, undated (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Day, Sarah (Coit), undated (Box 91, Folder 21-22)
    - Day, Sarah (Coit): photograph of silhouette, [1808?] (Box 92, Folder 23)
      See also: box 112, folder 103-104
    - Day, Thomas, undated (Box 92, Folder 25)
      See also: box 110, folder 93
    - Day, Thomas Mills, 1859, 1890 (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Day, Thomas (1777-1855): copy of painting, undated (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Day, Mrs. Thomas Mills [Ellen (Pomeroy) Day?], 1864 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Day, Thomas Mills, Jr., 1882 (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Day Family: album of photographs of, compiled by Ellen (Day) Bonaparte, undated (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - Day Family: unidentified, undated (Box 92, Folder 30)
    - [Day Family?], 1863 (Box 92, Folder 31)
    - Dean, Katharine Seymour (Parsons), 1875-1899, undated (Box 92, Folder 32)
      See also: box 94, folder 72
    - Dean, Katharine Seymour (Parsons): photograph album: Bombay, 1914 (Box 92, Folder 33)
    - Dean, Katharine Seymour (Parsons): Hilcroft pictures, undated (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - Dean, Katharine Seymour (Parsons): family, vacation scenes, 1929, undated (Box 93, Folder 35)
    - Ely, Mary (Day), undated (Box 93, Folder 36)
    - Ford Family: Alice, Burdette (Uncle), Burdette, Elizabeth, Rita, 1884, undated (Box 93, Folder 37)
    - Hemingway, Kate Stevens, 1916, undated (Box 93, Folder 38)
    - Hitchcock, Charles Edward, 1863-1880, undated (Box 93, Folder 39)
    - Hitchcock, Clara M., 1885 (Box 93, Folder 40)
    - [Hitchcock, Clara M.?]; Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour, undated (Box 93, Folder 41)
    - Hitchcock, Clarissa (Ford), 1865, undated (Box 93, Folder 42-43)
    - Hitchcock, Henry Valentine, undated (Box 93, Folder 44)
    - Hitchcock, Herbert Allan, undated (Box 93, Folder 45)
    - Hitchcock, John, undated (Box 93, Folder 46)
      See also: box 110, folder 94
    - Hitchcock, Lawrence, undated (Box 93, Folder 47)
    - Hitchcock, Lawrence Sill, 1899 (Box 93, Folder 48)
    - Hitchcock, Reuben, Circa 1880 (Box 93, Folder 49)
    - Hitchcock, Sarah Marshall, Circa 1880 (Box 93, Folder 50)
    - Hitchcock Family: Lawrence, Clarissa (Ford), John, Henry Valentine, Mary, Sarah Melissa Seymour, Circa 1850 (Box 93, Folder 51)
    - [Hitchcock Family?], 1859-1883, undated (Box 93, Folder 52)
    - Holley, Alexander, 1886, undated (Box 94, Folder 53)
    - Holley, Sarah Coit (Day), 1880-1892, undated (Box 94, Folder 54)
    - Howard, Sarah (Seymour), Circa 1920-1928 (Box 94, Folder 55)
    - Howard, Sarah (Seymour), [ca 1930?] (Box 94, Folder 56)
      See also: box 98, folder 123
      See also: box 98, folder 133
      See also: box 96, folder 101
    - Kelvin, Lord and Lady, 1902 (Box 94, Folder 57)
    - Ladd, Mattie, undated (Box 94, Folder 58)
    - Law, Mr. and Mrs. Charles, 1904 (Box 94, Folder 59)
    - Law, Ellen (Atwater); Charles Seymour, Jr.; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, 1914 (Box 94, Folder 60)
    - Leggett Family, undated (Box 94, Folder 61)
      See also: box 114, folder 16
    - Linklaen, Helen (Seymour), 1933 (Box 94, Folder 62)
    - Morley, Lizzie M. (Hitchcock), 1892 (Box 94, Folder 63)
    - Parsons, Charles Seymour, 1883-1894, undated (Box 94, Folder 64)
    - Parsons, Harriet Day, undated (Box 94, Folder 65)
      See also: box 91, folder 6
    - Parsons, Robert, 1886, 1897, undated (Box 94, Folder 66)
    - Parsons, Sarah (Seymour), 1888 (Box 94, Folder 67)
      See also: box 94, folder 70
    - [Parsons, Sarah (Seymour)?], [1930?] (Box 94, Folder 68)
    - Parsons, Seymour, 1934 (Box 94, Folder 69)
    - Parsons, William Cheney; Sarah (Seymour) Parsons; Thomas Day Seymour; Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour, 1895 (Box 94, Folder 70)
      See also: box 112, folder 102
    - Parsons, Willaim Edward, 1895 (Box 94, Folder 71)
    - Parsons Family: William Cheney, Sarah (Seymour), Katharine (Parsons) Dean, William Edward, Harriet Day, Charles S., Robert, 1889, undated (Box 94, Folder 72)
    - Perkins, Rev. Nathan (1749-1837): copy of portrait of, undated (Box 94, Folder 73)
    - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1884-1903, undated (Box 95, Folder 74-75)
      See also: box 109, folder 81-82
      See also: box 110, folder 95
    - St. John, Seymour; Charles Seymour, Jr., [1913?] (Box 95, Folder 76)
    - [St. John Family?], 1920, [1958?] (Box 95, Folder 77)
    - Seymour, Catharine (Perkins), undated (Box 95, Folder 78)
    - Seymour, Charles, II (1777-1852), undated (Box 95, Folder 79)
      See also: box 110, folder 96
      See also: box 111, folder 97
    - Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1862-1863, undated (Box 95, Folder 80)
      See also: box 100, folder 150
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963): boyhood portraits, Circa 1887-1897, undated (Box 95, Folder 81)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963): Trinity Church camping trip, 1898 (Box 95, Folder 82)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1902 (Box 95, Folder 83)
      See also: box 109, folder 90
      See also: box 109, folder 83
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963): Cambridge friends, 1903 (Box 95, Folder 84)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963): Yale freshman crew, 1905 (Box 95, Folder 85)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963): Versailles, 1919 (Box 96, Folder 86)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), [ca 1920?] (Box 96, Folder 87)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1924 (Box 96, Folder 88)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), [1920's?] (Box 96, Folder 89)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963): photograph of portrait by Edgaforeff, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 90)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), [1930's?] (Box 96, Folder 91)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1937 (Box 96, Folder 92)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), [1950's?] (Box 96, Folder 93)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), [1950's] (Box 96, Folder 94)
      See also: box 114, folder 6
      See also: box 109, folder 84
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1961 (Box 96, Folder 95)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); Gladys (Watkins) Seymour, [1911-1920?] (Box 96, Folder 96)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); Gladys (Watkins) Seymour, [ca 1930?] (Box 96, Folder 97)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); Gladys (Watkins) Seymour; Charles Seymour, Jr., 1912-1913 (Box 96, Folder 98)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); Charles Seymour, Jr.; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, [1915-1917?] (Box 96, Folder 99)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); Gladys (Watkins) Seymour; Charles Seymour, Jr., [1925?] (Box 96, Folder 100)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); Gladys (Watkins) Seymour; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour; Sarah (Seymour) Howard, undated (Box 96, Folder 101)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); Georges Clemenceau, [1923?] (Box 96, Folder 102)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); Palmer York, 1906-1907 (Box 96, Folder 103)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); 1908 classmates, 1914 (Box 96, Folder 104)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963); four other college presidents, 1941 (Box 96, Folder 105)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963): photographs taken by, aboard S.S. Finland, 1905 (Box 96, Folder 106)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963): photographs taken by, on trip to Norway, 1908 (Box 96, Folder 107)
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr., [1912-1930], 1931, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 108-113)
      See also: box 94, folder 60
      See also: box 96, folder 98-100
      See also: box 98, folder 132
      See also: box 100, folder 158
      See also: box 109, folder 85
      See also: box 109, folder 88
      See also: box 91, folder 15
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr.; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, 1918-1919, undated (Box 97, Folder 114)
      See also: box 114, folder 13
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr.; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour; Molly Barnes, 1914, undated (Box 97, Folder 115)
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr.; photographs of Europe, copies of paintings, 1905-1906, undated (Box 97, Folder 116-118)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater, [1914-1920, 1935, circa 1950?] (Box 97, Folder 119-121)
      See also: box 96, folder 99
      See also: box 97, folder 114-115
      See also: box 98, folder 132-133
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater, in the O.S.S., 1944-1945 (Box 98, Folder 122)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater; Sarah (Seymour) Howard, [1925?] (Box 98, Folder 123)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater; friends, 1931-1933 (Box 98, Folder 124)